

+94 71 999 1002

mmifas@gmail.com

No 12/1 Athurs Place, Dehiwala Sri Lanka

Q github.com/mifas

goo.gl/tBZbvJ
 goo

SUMMERY

I am a full stack developer with over 5 years of experience. I have developed and maintained complex Web and RESTful applications using PHP, Laravel, MySQL, and JavaScript along with various other technologies. Most of the projects I've implemented most common design patterns with Twitter Bootstrap, SASS and webpack2.

I always love working with a technically strong team where I can solve complex problems with a good balance of freedom and responsibility. and ability to learn new technology within a short period.

EXPERIENCE

Riverview: Mobile Loyalty and engagement

Senior PHP Developer

riverviewms.com

MAR 2015 - PRESENT

2 YRS - 4 MOS

Startup company for Loyalty management. This is a SaaS products. Working with back-end development team to engage clients and customers experience providing new solutions using AWS and some other latest technologies. working with the mobile development team and develop APIs and back-end features to solve platform based problems.

3CS: Web Design

PHP Developer

3cs.lk

JUN 2012 - FEB 2015

2 YRS - 9 MOS

- Mabroc Teas Order Management System
 An internal system, powered by Codelgniter using MVC architecture, which has the ability to manage customers, supplier, products, and orders. Additionally, have Purchase Invoice, Goods receive note and Commercial Invoice.
- VKE Inventory Control System
 An internal system powered by Codelgniter using MVC architecture, which is for managing customers, stores, and products. Screenshots.
- The Kingsbury Hotel Hotel Site
 A hotel website powered by FuelCMS with an online booking engine
- Elephant Corridor Hotel Site
 A hotel website with an online booking engine developed through vanilla PHP
- Babynames.lk
 A website for baby names, Payment & eZ cache gateway integrations & multilingual. Written in Codelgniter

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Backend developments

- PHP 5.4+, Frameworks (Laravel, Codeigniter, Wordpress, FuelCMS)
- Node.js, Framworks (expres.js, adonis.js)
- xDebug, Unit testing with PHPUnit, TDD, Design patterns, Template engines(handlebars.js)
- REST API and Microservices

Frontend developments

• HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Vue.js, Webpack2, LESS, SASS, Twitter bootstrap, RegEx

Databases/ Version Control/ Other

- DB: MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB
- VCS: Git
- Worked with Amazon EC2, S3, SQS

EDUCATION & QUALIFICATION

Postgraduate Diploma | BCS, The Chartered Institute for IT

SEP 2011 - MAR 2014

Sun Certified Java Programmer (SCJP 1.5)

2009

PCJT & J2EE | Institute of Java and Technological Studies (IJTS)

2008 - 2009

REFERENCES

Tariq Cassim

Head of Department, Software and Services DHI Group Singapore +65 9100 9564 | tariq@tntglobal.com.sg

Priyanjith Asanka

Associate Tech Lead Riverview Mobility Solutions +94 77 297 6060 | priyanjith849@gmail.com